华星国际
可不简单呢当然了
这华星国际呀可是华星商会
数值亿万
李青啊李青
难道你还想跟我男朋友比吗
你男朋友是华星国际的人
我怎么不知道我呸
你算老几啊
你跟我男朋友都不是一个级别的人
怎么会有资格认识他
你说的对
确实不是一个级别
Maybe he's not good enough
You waste it with me
Dare to touch porcelain my boyfriend
Li Qing, I ask you now
Throw me this trash
I didn't want to see him again.
Impossible Qiurong
Are you going too far?
I am too much
We are all high society people
If it weren't for you
I can eat at the same table with this loser
There's no shame in that.
Oh, that's right.
This crescent moon has a poor sour taste
Let me see if you don't eat this meal
If you don't like it, get out of here
Who yells so loudly and dares to coax Lao Tzu's woman?